{
    "id": "c56351524d4243c18345fee1ad885d3f",
    "title": "Both, Either, Neither",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "...................... of them were ill so they stayed at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like ..................... of these colors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t decide between these gowns. I like them ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... Angelina nor Jennifer turned up today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Neither",
                "Either"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can take ………………….. the bus or the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. John nor Peter could solve the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Either",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... my parents enjoy riding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Neither",
                "Either"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has invited us …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… dances and sings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}